// creating an array and passing the number, questions, options, and answers
let questions = [
  {
  numb: 1,
  question: "Class based requirements modeling method describes,",
  answer: "All of the mentioned above",
  options: [
    "Object and its state",
    "All of the mentioned above",
    "Class of objects",
    "Data attributes that describe the object"
  ]
},
  {
  numb: 2,
  question: "A ___ builds the class-based model using requirements elicited from the customer",
  answer: "Software engineer or an analyst",
  options: [
    "Network engineer",
    "Software engineer or an analyst",
    "Architect",
    "Tester"
  ]
},
  {
  numb: 3,
  question: "Class responsibility collaborator (CRC) modeling describes,",
  answer: "Both A and B",
  options: [
    "Identification and organization of the classes those are relevant to system",
    "Product requirements",
    "Both A and B",
    "None of the mentioned above"
  ]
},
  {
  numb: 4,
  question: " The ___ of a class that describe the characteristics of the class that has been selected for inclusion in the analysis model.",
  answer: "Attributes",
  options: [
    "Entity",
    "Attributes",
    "Flow lines",
    "None of these"
  ]
},
  {
  numb: 5,
  question: "  The degree of any vertex of graph is ________" ,
  answer: "The number of edges incident with vertex",
  options: [
    "The number of edges incident with vertex",
    "Number of vertex in a graph",
    "Number of vertices adjacent to that vertex",
    "Number of edges in a graph",

    
  ]
},
{
  numb: 6,
  question: "  Which of the following statements is/are TRUE for an undirected graph? P: Number of odd degree vertices is even Q: Sum of degrees of all vertices is even" ,
  answer: "Operations",
  options: [
    "Operations",
    "Process flow",
    "Software design",
    "Neither of the above"
  ]
},
{
  numb: 7,
  question: "An analysis package is," ,
  answer: "Both A and B",
  options: [
    "Analysis modeling categorization",
    "Group of analysis package",
    "Both A and B",
    "None of the mentioned above"
  ]
},

{
  numb: 8,
  question: "Amongst which of the following is / are UML modeling notation can be applied," ,
  answer: "All of the mentioned above",
  options: [
    "To define hierarchiese",
    "To define relationships",
    "To define associations and aggregations",
    "All of the mentioned above"
  ]
},

{
  numb: 9,
  question: "The nature of an object define by,"  ,
  answer: "Operations",
  options: [
    "Software design",
    "Operations",
    "Process flow",
    "None Of the above"
  ]
},
{
  numb: 10,
  question: "Amongst which of the following is / are the Garvinâ€™s Quality Dimensions, " ,
  answer: "	All of the mentioned above",
  options: [
    "Performance Quality, Feature quality",
    "Reliability, Conformance",
    "Durability, Serviceability",
    "All of the mentioned above"
  ]
},



// you can uncomment the below codes and make duplicate as more as you want to add question
// but remember you need to give the numb value serialize like 1,2,3,5,6,7,8,9.....

//   {
//   numb: 6,
//   question: "Your Question is Here",
//   answer: "Correct answer of the question is here",
//   options: [
//     "Option 1",
//     "option 2",
//     "option 3",
//     "option 4"
//   ]
// },
];